JOSE PEREIRA

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

I've always been Interested in web development since I was 14 years old and have always been fascinated by being able to create things through programming and being able to impact society with it.

Miami, FL (305)842-8813 jmanuelpereira2@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/jmanuelper github.com/Jmanuelpereira

TECHNICAL SKILLS

JavaScript, React.js, Express.js, MongoDB, Node.js, HTML, CSS, SCSS,AJAX, jQuery,Responsive Design Bootstrap, Git, GitHub, Wordpress, Photoshop and Networking

English and Spanish.

EDUCATION

2014 - 2014 • Bellinsoft PHP level I and PHP level II course

2014 - 2016 • Universidad Bicentenaria de Aragua System Engineering

2019 - 2020 • Ironhack Miami Web Developer Bootcamp

Projects developed

Galaxy Finder

It is an educational and interactive game about the universe.

Technologies used: Javascript, HTML, CSS. AJAX

DOM Game: https://jmanuelpereira.github.io/Project1/

IronCaller

It is an application for reminders through phone calls.

Technologies used: Javascript, HTML, CSS. AJAX, Mongo DB, Boostrap, Node.js, Express.js Express App: https://ironcaller.herokuapp.com/

DealerSoft

It is an application for the sale of used and new vehicles online.

Technologies used: JavaScript, React.js, Express.js, MongoDB, Node.js, HTML, CSS, SCSS,AJAX, jQuery,Responsive Design Bootstrap

MERN App: https://dealersoft.herokuapp.com/

EXPERIENCE

06/2014 - 11/2014 Adonai Auto Parts

Web Developer

- Development of new systems and pages for the company website
- Keep the website online and working
- Development of a admin side for no-programmers use.

11/2017 - 2020 Gripert

IT Manager

- Coordinate the work team to serve customers
- Review each job before approval
- Manage digital resources of the company to give better performance